Guide to the William Hane Wannamaker Papers, 1917 - 1948 UA.05.52.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject File, 1926-1946
  - Naval ROTC, Duke University, undated (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Personnel Dept., Duke University, undated (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Physical Education, Duke University, undated (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - President's Report, Duke University
    - 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 314)
    - 1938-1939 (2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 315-316)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 317)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 318)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Publications Council, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Religious Emphasis Week, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Schedule of Courses, Duke University, 1936-1938, undated (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Student Grades, Duke University, 1933-1941 (Box 28, Folder 324)
    Includes statistical information on grades, not personally identifiable information.
  - Student Health Dept., Duke University, 1935-1942 (Box 28, Folder 325)
  - Student Honors, Duke University, 1935-1947 (Box 28, Folder 326)
  - Student Scholarship Committee, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 327)
  - Teacher-Course Evalutions, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 328)
  - Tuition, Duke University, circa 1946 (Box 28, Folder 329)
  - Undergraduate Scholarship Committee, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 330)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Council, Duke University, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 331)
  - Woman's Student Forum, Duke University, undated (Box 28, Folder 332)